you know the jungle's getting pretty
insane we got fairy factory big custom
trees even
bigger tree
we got a tower we got spanner works over
there
and of course the giant mansion and a
whole lot more work that needs to be
done to it now today i would love to get
this room
settled into place because
it's uh it's gonna be the main room of
my base i will spend most of my time
here and it's gonna have all of my items
in and i really need to get going on
this i keep putting it off now it's time
to prepare
i
am going to go and gather a bunch of
stuff let's go
[Music]
okay so we got a bunch of the terracotta
together and a bit of sandstone
and we also have over here about a
million chests i have no idea how many
chests i need but
this i don't think will even scratch the
surface because you need hoppers and you
need normal chests but something really
really weird happened during this whole
thing i was there cutting the trees
maybe you saw a big gap in the time
lapse where nothing happened hmm
well i went over to scar's base and
i didn't say i and i started recording
and he was basically floating around i
don't know what was going on he was just
hopping and jumping and flying with no
items whatsoever i tried killing him and
he just flew back in it was so
strange eventually it got sorted out
though and i helped him and i cured
scars villagers now to get going on this
i need to get some dye in order to
make all of these terracotta cyan
terracotta so let's use the wizard fruit
because i think it's my favorite way to
travel and go to the shopping district
all right and there's a special order
double chest of both gravel and sand
will pay for delivery let me know price
oh boy have we not got enough of that
here we've got one
i mean i'll just take this to xb this
bit and gravel okay probably not enough
gravel yeah we could we can do a little
delivery but what we really came here
for was welcome to color complete i
think it's concrete and dies so that's
cool
that was amazing that was absolutely
amazing
i thought i was dying
okay so i need blue dye
uh let's go one two three
there we go four diamonds
and then does it does this turn off when
i leave
oh my goodness
okay i think we got what we need and now
we can just quickly zip back to the base
all right here we go so we can turn all
this into cyan terracotta and we can get
started on bringing up the walls of this
room i don't know what's gonna happen
with this but we'll figure that out
later on for now
let's just start the time lapse and get
this thing underway
[Applause]
[Music]
this room has been completely
transformed admittedly it's a giant cube
with absolutely no detailing or light
but finally
we have a proper space to work with
now i have replicated this thing over to
the left and that does present some
design challenges it might be an idea to
have like a cave
sprawling out of this because it is
meant to be underground after all i
could just sort of continue this shape
all the way down and it could be like a
natural pillar not entirely sure the
other option is to box it in and pretend
like it doesn't exist but now this thing
is really starting to get in the way so
i'll leave this to collect one last time
and then gotta say goodbye to this
so this is where the item sort is going
to be now i really wanted to start it
today and maybe i will be able to a bit
later on
but i can't start it until i have the
materials for it and it turns out you
need a lot of hoppers and a lot of
chests and a lot of knowledge i've no
i've no idea i just saw that guy
sneaking in the background i have no
idea
how to make an item sorter so i'm gonna
have to do a bit of research as well and
also in the time lapse you may have
noticed that scar helped me out with
some more terrain i mean i did this
stuff on the outside but he did like
this this little bit here in the middle
looking pretty cool and so it finally
matches on the exterior check it out
it's really starting to get symmetrical
so what i'm gonna do is head over to
mumbo's iron farm he said i could use it
when i needed to because um yeah iron
farms can be a bit laggy on the server
so we're kind of sharing so what i'm
gonna do is go over to his iron farm oh
my goodness i forgot about these things
they're terrifying and and beautiful so
i'm gonna leave my camera account here
so that this can like load up loads of
iron and then this will be what i use to
make my item sorter so while this is
loaded and slowly trickling in the iron
i've heard from b dubs and scar and we
are about to meet up to build the town
hall which is very exciting so we're
going to zip over to the shopping
district right now to go meet up with
them
[Music]
where am i
that was quite an entrance there all
right so
guys we are well we are here to
hopefully build up the town hall you
guys got my my letter my signs i did
yeah yeah i got that but i'm also
missing some things too okay so the town
hall what we're gonna do
is i've got a bunch of resources with me
loads of bricks i got loads of grass
blocks hopefully what we need and what
we need is a building big enough to put
all of this in
all of this
daimong days in what
go careful all right then yeah we we can
do that we should do that anyone want to
wait you're in it you don't want to
break me out
[Laughter]
it's hollow it's a diamond heist over
here
i don't think we need to be scared of it
because we're going to be moving this
anyway we got to take all of this down
and move it over oh my have you ever
tasted diamonds like just went up there
and just gave it a little lick
no no no dude it's tasty just give it a
give it a try no this is one of those
wizard things this is a wizard
this is a wizard thing hey hey you know
you know don't don't believe me but i'm
just going to enjoy the taste of
diamonds over here that's fine
so beat up should we do this um and
leave him to
yeah you can lick that and then we'll
build it did you want any of these
shulker boxes full of supplies
should we choose a spot i was thinking
behind the redstone shop because it's
like the only place that's got enough
space yeah it's getting a little crowded
here a bit disorganized to be quite
frank
and um
that's kind of why we need someone for
mayor and i'll tell you i'll tell you
what i've got something to show you
fellas boom
mumbo wow
what better man to organize the shopping
district that's a really that's really
nice this is the most subtle this is the
mustache that serves you you know
wait a second
is that his back head hair it is it is
it's not actually the mustache no it's
not the it's the it's the bargain stash
this is the one from the back of his
head anyway we're gonna be building the
town hall and then uh hopefully we can
get everyone to support mumbo really
yes the sun is setting we have to
this is my service to the community
[Laughter]
don't do that this is important
there's going to be things in the sky
phantoms and you'll see don't
don't
hey you owe me some doors what
yeah let's start this yeah then dude
let's stop this let's start this
building okay all right yeah let's start
to build in the morning
[Music]
okay i'm out i'm out of punch range i'm
out of punch range all right go go for
it let's go
we'll stand over here
all right have a great night's sleep
guys
okay okay okay okay okay come on scott
we'll leave it here all the way okay
okay okay we're over here we're over
here we're good hollow out thank you
can't you everything's really precarious
perfect yes it's a wonderful morning
it's time to build
[Music]
how many how many hours six six hours
later in one six oh okay that's a lot
yeah
but look at this look what we made
together
i like it it's beautiful i really like
it i'm not gonna lie i think i think we
nailed this uh i think we've uh we've
left let's go and have a look inside
we've kind of left the interior
um up for imagination shall we say yeah
yeah just there we got this nice got
this nice elevation it like kind of
looks over the shoulder oh wow look at
that look at that view you get a key
that's a beauty you get a good view of
the shopping district but the the
highlight here is the diamond throne
the seat of power on the server i mean
this is forget mayor this is what we're
really after on the server right
yes not the title we're after we're
after the the seat the diamond throne ah
scar oh
this is nice
like you look nice up there he's easy
thank you he's all decked out with his
armor and he blends in
oh yeah i i feel at home up here
i like it i like it a lot you look at
home up there don't get any don't get
any ideas remember why there we go
that's right oh of course
oh right for sure right there's only one
one piece of facial hair that's going to
end up on that throne
yeah this is good i like this i like it
we're all a little delirious am i right
yeah it's it's it's been it's been a
long night it's been a it's been a crazy
long night but i really like how the the
light comes down and hits just hits the
diamonds everything else is dark thank
goodness that this is on a mushroom
island because otherwise there'd be
there'd be uh mobs everywhere
yeah yeah we'd be infesting the the
shopping district it'd be bad i think we
should probably leave some i'll i'll put
some signs here later on explaining
you know that you've got to vote for
mumbo
later on the line you know have a
have a popularity chart or something so
people can come cast their vote skull
get down
oh oh yeah get down i feel attractive he
looks really nice up there off limits
off limits
okay all right i'll stay off i'll stay
home i don't know i i feel like i this
is it's kind of cozy nut it is get give
it a taste give it a lick give it a
little look
i'm not licking it you sicko should we
tell him grian we were building this and
for two hours straight he was over there
licking the dice
disgusting it's been 24 hours since we
built this and i've got to say upon
coming back i think this is a superb
build i was so tired by the time we
actually finished that i i barely even
remember what we did and some additions
have been made since i was gone so i
guess b-dubs and scar added a few things
like a like a really nice garden here a
couple more trees at the front and
overall
this is going to serve
its purpose it kind of it kind of
dominates the shopping district which is
really really cool and it was awesome to
do a build project like this with three
people all at the same time i don't
think i've ever done that quite on this
scale five hours it took and of course
the diamond throne i always wanted to do
this okay look i need to i need to get
right just the right angle for this and
then get my camera account see
you think you have diamonds
pathetic
imagine this is like if someone if
someone was here and he's like meh can i
have some diamonds
no
no you can't have diamonds see this is
why i shouldn't occupy the diamond
throne i am uh i'm probably not meant to
be in charge of this insane amount of
diamonds however
someone who would uh
be ideal
is mumbo jumbo leo so i'm gonna take
this map we're gonna make a bunch of
copies and we are gonna start
campaigning by putting a bunch of them
around the shopping district but first
people that uh come across the diamond
throne might be a little bit confused so
i'm going to quickly add a few signs
i know that b-dubs is going to come back
here and do some interior work to this
so i'm just going to do a bunch of
temporary signs in case anyone is
interested
i've written down some information the
diamond throne has been placed in the
shopping district someone must take the
seat and make decisions about the place
who will that be we decide a date will
be announced later so that we can cast
our vote for who we want to be mayor
anyone can run but only one can occupy
the throne
vote mumbo for mayor
just casually put that in it kind of
stands out a little bit but you know we
need to get we need to get as many votes
for mumbo as possible and i was actually
thinking um we could uh we could put
some we could put some campaign promises
next to next to the vote now this is one
of the uh the most visited portals i
haven't actually managed to link that
one up properly but hopefully someone
someone who knows portals better than me
can help me out with that so mumbo for
mayor the suit that serves you lots of
propaganda going on so i've actually got
quite a lot of these posters to put
around
so probably one in the more more popular
spots i could put one here oh yeah i
need to totally need to send that i'll
do that after this
he promises
free facial
hair
for all supporters
boom
who doesn't want a free mustache
who doesn't want a free mustache mumbo
for meh these little extra added things
are just great he is a face you could
trust he's online right now look at look
at that face and another good point is
we could use the hermit herald over
there to promote the campaign
don't really know how it works maybe
i'll get in touch with
with cleo because look you can advertise
here pretty cheap and you can even get a
happy son so that might be a good idea
and also while we're here vote for mumbo
vote for mumbo vote for mumbo and vote
for mumbo and another sign
the man
definitely
with a plan he has no plan of the sorts
i wonder what mumbo's gonna think when
he sees this
let's just put a couple of posters on
people's portals because they're more
likely to see them there oh maybe even
one by the button
we'll save some we'll save the rest for
later shall we kind of i've kind of put
a lot of posters around oh wait this is
this is mumbo's portal
he's gonna like this
he's gonna find out so i might as well
go all in
he's definitely running for mayor look
at that hair
all right i'm going to save these i need
to make that quick delivery over to xb
and then i think that's uh more than
enough
for today it's been
it's been a very busy and heavy episode
man i did not expect to get quite this
much done
we have we have made some significant
progress gathering and building the
interior of the base and even a little
bit of terrain and we went and got
the the mayor for mumbo why do i keep
saying that mumbo for mayor
we got that campaign rolling with the
town hall right so let's go and do this
delivery took me ages to find it in the
the mess that is my base
but i found it right let's go and
deliver this how much we gonna charge oh
he's there
i was wondering what that noise was all
right this must be his his area so i see
three things we've got to do first thing
is mumbo for mayor the second thing i
got to take these doors and then third
thing is i need to make this delivery
this is so funny he has no idea that i'm
even here
there we go the cost is 59 diamonds
please please return the shulkers
because there's 27
27 and so 27 plus 27 and then a couple
of diamonds on for delivery so job done
uh xp i know you're down there delivery
done
okay and i think that is it for today's
episode my goodness has it been busy all
i've got to say is thank you very much
for watching i hope you enjoyed this
episode and i shall see you
in the next one good bye